Finding Aid for McHugh and Hoffman records, 1957-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence
  - 1985-1989
    - WVTM Birmingham (Box 56)
    - WVVE New Orleans (Box 56)
    - WXFL Tampa (Box 56)
    - WXYZ Detroit (Box 57)
  - Canadian Correspondence 1981-1989
    - ATV Halifax 1981-1989 (Box 57)
    - British Columbia Association of Broadcasters 1986 (Box 57)
    - CFCF Montreal 1987-1988 (Box 57)
    - CFCM Quebec 1988-1989 (Box 57)
    - CITI Toronto 1977-1989 (Box 57)
    - CITI Toronto 1977-1989 (cont.) (Box 58)
    - CJOH Ottawa 1985-1988 (Box 58)
    - CKO Halifax 1989 (Box 58)
    - CKSH Sherbrooke, Quebec 1989 (Box 58)
    - CKTM Trois-Rivieres 1988 (Box 58)
    - CKTV Regina, Saskatchewan 1988 (Box 58)
    - CKVR Barrie, Ontario 1982-1988 (Box 58)
    - CKX Brandon, Manitoba 1985-1986 (Box 58)
    - CKY Winnipeg, Manitoba 1993 (Box 58)
    - Cogeko Group, Inc. 1985 (Box 59)
    - Manitoba Television Network 1987 (Box 59)
  - England
    - Five-TV Ltd. 1992 (Box 59)
  - Luxembourg
    - RTL 1983 (Box 59)
  - National Network Correspondence
    - American Broadcasting Company 1980-1989 (Box 59)
      (incl. Hispanic Viewer Study)
    - Cable News Network 1988 (Box 59)
    - KPR 1986 (Box 59)
    - McGraw-Hill Broadcasting 1976-1979 (Box 59)
    - National Broadcasting Company (Box 59)
    - News Information Wire Service 1981-1986 (Box 60)
    - Spanish International Network 1981-1982 (Box 60)
    - Westinghouse Broadcasting 1981 (Box 60)
  - Storer Cable
    - 1962-1982 (Box 60)
      (incl. Sex and Violence on Television: A Viewer's Reaction, 1969)
    - 1962-1982 (cont.) (Box 61)
    - How People Use Television Program Promotions 1963 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous
    - The Telepictures Times 1982-1983 (Box 61)
- McHugh and Hoffman Business Files
  The McHugh and Hoffman Business Files series (1 ft.) dates mainly from the 1990's, although there is some earlier material, including promotional materials and items from a conference that was organized by McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. and TV Digest, Inc. in the 1980's.
  - American Research Bureau Contact Report 1964-1965 (Box 61)
  - Articles 1990-1992 (Box 61)
  - The Business of TV News Conference, Sponsored by McHugh and Hoffman and TV Digest, Inc.
    - 1984 (Box 62)
    - 1985 (Box 62)
    - 1986 (Box 62)
    - 1989 (Box 62)
  - CATPAC 1992 (Box 62)
  - Finance / Equipment 1992, 1993 (Box 62)
  - High Tech Seminars 1994 (Box 62)
  - Hollywood PA Test, Daytime Talk Shows (Box 62)
  - Information Highway 1993, 1994 (Box 62)
  - Late Night Television Research Conducted by MSI 1992 (Box 62)
  - Manuscripts
    - The 5 % Factor (Box 62)
    - Introducing 100 Plus, A Research and Consulting Service (Box 62)
    - Mrs. Jones Script (Box 62)
  - Marketing Strategies, Inc. (MSI), Business Meetings and Correspondence 1991-1994 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1990-1994 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Jack Bowen 1990-1993 (Box 62)
  - Old Client Lists for Reference (Box 62)
  - Presentation Materials (Box 62)
  - Research Issues 1994-1995 (Box 62)
  - Television Personality Surveys (Box 62)
    (incl. "Why McHugh and Hoffman, Inc.")